Thirty years ago,
an unprecedented disaster called
a "spatial quake" assaulted our world.
Brought about unintentionally,
or perhaps done on purpose,
the female life-forms which
caused them were called "Spirits."
And their very existence was
kept secret from the public.
And now...
...I, Shido Itsuka...
Go on and taste it, Shido!
No need to hold back! Eat, eat!
"Episode One:
'The Seventh Spirit'"
Um... This is...?
Foolish. It's stew.
We wanted to make some food
for Shido, so we all put it together.
Well, I appreciate the thought, but...
What the heck's in here
to give it that color?
We went all out this time.
Everyone tossed in the food they love best.
I-Isn't that wonderful, Shido?
For them to make you something so yummy...
Come on! Eat while it's hot!
You contribute, too, Kotori!
Make an offering to complete this banquet!
Eh?
Uh...
Ooh! Kotori put in something, too!
It's looking better and better!
Huh, what?
How is it, Shido?!
Surprisingly good!
Yay!
--We did it!
--I'm happy...
Thanks, everyone!
I knew Yuzuru's fried chicken
would bring the taste together.
Negative. It was Kaguya's pork cutlet.
That's what makes it so savory.
Huh?! No, it was yours...
Insist. It was Kaguya's.
You two never change...
Let's just call it a miracle collaboration
that took everyone's help!
They said on TV that stew is good
no matter what you put in, and it's true!
Must be, for something
of this color to be edible...
It's a shame that Miku
couldn't be here to join us.
Can't be helped with her work.
Darling!
Did you call me?!
Huh?!
Hi!
I heard all of your lonely calls!
So the Spirit idol, Miku Izayoi,
has made her appearance at last!
--Miku?!
--Huh?
Then you singing is...
A recording that looks like it's live!
Anyways, what are all of you doing?
Are you having a party,
all together like this?
Oh! Speaking of which, I'm pretty
sure it's my birthday today!
All I want for a present
is a hot kiss from everyone!
Huh? Wh-What are you doing?!
Defense. Kaguya Barrier.
W-Wait!
Stop it, Miku! Get back in the TV at once!
--Yuzuru!
--Come on, don't be shy!
--That's enough, Miku!
--I need you for Kaguya Barrier.
--Let me go!
--I said stop!
Cut it out!
Oof.
I see!
So that's why you're all having stew!
Anyways, it's good to have you here.
It's hot, so be extra careful.
Oh, my, what a peculiar color.
Here goes nothing!
H-Hot!
Are you okay?! That's why I warned you...
Darling... I seem to have
burned my poor lips.
Unless you kiss them, they'll never heal...
What are you on about, Miku?!
That's not how burns work!
Pain.
Shido, I have also burnt my lips.
Need urgent care.
Hey, no fair!
Ouch!
Hey, Shido. Don't forget Yoshino!
Shido!
I accidentally burnt my lips as well!
You guys...
Big brother...
I think I did, too...
White ribbon out of nowhere!
Eek! Is everyone all right?!
Don't worry, I'll make you
all feel better right away!
Hey!
O-Origami?!
I made stew, too.
You did?
Th-Thank you.
It's turtle, scorpion, and seal body parts...
...boiled in energy drink.
Please tell me your thoughts
the next time we meet.
That's right.
Though ripe with trouble,
the passing days were fulfilling...
Shido.
Now then.
Let's begin our date.
You all set, Shido?
Yeah. Whenever you're ready.
How do I put it...
So eerie.
This park has been abandoned
since the Great Spatial Quake.
It's far enough from redevelopment
that it's still untouched to this day.
Then it's as it was 30 years ago...
The Spirit moved from the spatial quake's
origin to that area somewhere.
Make contact before the AST shows up.
Roger that.
--What the heck?!
--What is it?
This can't be what it was like...
There's just no way...
It's faint, but we're detecting
spirit waves nearby.
What you're seeing was
manifested by a Spirit's powers.
You hearing that, Shido?
The Spirit we're after is close by.
Oh?
How rare a sight.
Usually when I get pulled here,
I never meet anyone but the AST.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I'm not going to eat you or anything.
U-Um, I'm...
Eh? You're actually kinda cute.
Why are you in a place like this?
Aren't there alarms to take
shelter when a Spirit appears?
Th-That's...
Shido, our choices!
"1. For one reason only. To meet you.
2. I-I don't know. I escaped late and ended up here...
3. Since you're here, can I fondle your boobs?"
Make your choice, everyone!
"1. For one reason only. To meet you.
2. I-I don't know. I escaped late and ended up here...
3. Since you're here, can I fondle your boobs?"
Well, this one was straightforward.
It's gotta be one!
Without knowing her temperament,
it's best to act normal.
Wrong! We should go with choice two!
This Spirit is a big sister type.
It might be surprising, but Shido
can tickle maternal instincts!
Mmm, mmm!
That has some truth to it.
Though, I'm shocked...
Not a single person chose three?
Figured Kannazuki at least
would pick that as a joke.
Budding breasts are supreme!
Such floppy boobs like
that don't interest me!
If it was to lick the back of her knee,
I'd have second thoughts, but...
Oh?
No!
Thank you very yes!
Shido, number two.
Say it with puppy eyes as best as you can.
Eh?
What's the matter?
U-Um, I...
I don't know...
I escaped late and ended up here...
Hmm?
Is that so?
What's your name?
Shido Itsuka.
Shido then.
Such a cute name.
I'm Natsumi.
Though I guess some of you
folks are calling me Witch.
Ms. Natsumi?
That sounds so stiff.
Natsumi is fine.
Hey, Shido...
Big Sis here wants to ask
you a little something.
May I?
S-Sure, go ahead.
Do you... think that I'm pretty?
Eh?
Y-Yeah...
I think you're very pretty.
I knew it! What specifically?
Shido, what part of Big Sis
do you think is pretty?
Um, that's...
Your almond eyes...
How your nose is so straight...
Your feminine style...
What else? What else?!
And... your hair... is so silky.
Yes!
Shido, you're right on the money!
Right...
I knew it...
This me... is pretty...
Shido!
It's the AST!
Oh?
It's okay.
Let's get to work, Haniel!
That's...
Take this!
Huh?!
What happened?!
Come, Shido.
Let's escape while we can.
You'll give Big Sis a lot
more compliments, won't you?
Uh, yeah...
I don't mind doing that, but...
Ah...
Achoo!
The surveillance camera is inoperable!
We'll restore it briefly!
Didn't see that coming.
You okay, Natsumi?
Shido, it's an emergency!
Natsumi's happiness meter is plummeting!
You saw, right?
Eh?
Don't play dumb!
You saw my...
Unforgivable...
You won't get away with it.
Shido Itsuka!
Your life... It's about to be over for good!
Why did she just vanish like that?
Hmm?
It's already lunch break?
Those strategy meetings for dealing
with Natsumi went all night...
Hmm?
Wh-What?
How dare you show your face, Shido Itsuka!
Don't you know what you've done?!
That's so lame.
What gives? What is this about?
You have some nerve to play dumb!
Making lewd passes at innocent Ai!
Embarrassing the hell out of Mai and Mii!
And not just that! Even Tohka was
a victim of your heinous crimes!
That's so lame!
H-Hold on a second!
I was busy with stuff
and just got to school!
You should know when to fess up!
Shido... What's done is done.
But you shouldn't pretend it didn't happen!
N-Next time, give me a heads up.
That way, I can prepare my heart first.
No, I'm telling you I didn't...
Origami?!
Don't tell me I did something to you, too!
Nothing...
I see...
Wh-What do you think you're
doing, Origami Tobiichi?!
Origami...?
But you just said I didn't do anything!
Right.
So I'll have you do it now.
Eh?!
Yes... Do everything you did to me, too.
Push me against the wall...
Lift up my chin...
Whisper sweet words into my ear...
Gently peeling up my skirt...
We exchange a deep, romantic kiss...
You pull off my clothes,
steal my innocence as a woman...
And leave your everlasting mark...
...imbued within my body.
Wait up! He hasn't done
that to anybody yet!
Do it, Shido.
Do it.
Now listen here...
There you are, Shido!
If there's one thing you are,
it's ballsy to stick around!
Warning. You'll pay for what you've done.
Kaguya! Yuzuru!
Don't tell me you think I
did something to you, too?!
Feigning ignorance?!
You better give back the
panties you stole from me!
Grudge.
Who else threw water on me saying
"I have a wet shirt fetish"?
Huh?! I would never do that!
To think he has no bounds...
This goes way beyond horsing around!
That's so lame.
In any case, we won't stand for this!
It's a crime to defy us Yamai!
And you'll have to pay for it!
More specifically, I'll
strip off your undies.
Response.
Additionally, I shall use this
spray bottle to soak your entire body.
No... I didn't do anything!
Itsuka...
I can't become a bride anymore!
You have to take responsibility!
Even Ms. Tammie?!
Itsuka...
About earlier... Were you actually serious?
I... dunno what to say.
You... gotta be kidding me!
He escaped!
Don't let 'em live!
That's so lame!
What in the world is happening?!
W-Wait!
Yo.
That was quick.
Who... are you?!
I was having all sorts of fun
while you were away.
You... What are you?!
What are you after by impersonating me?!
Is it funny?!
It is, in fact.
After all...
Dumb Shido still hasn't realized it.
That voice... Natsumi?!
Ding ding! That's right!
Surely you know why I've
impersonated you by now.
Don't tell me...
Shido Itsuka!
Your life... It's about to be over for good!
Did you do all those crazy things
so I couldn't live here anymore?
Pitiful. Twenty points.
Then why?
Shido...
Don't you think it's strange
to have two of the same person?
Unless there's just one of us,
everyone will be so confused.
Eh?
From now on, I'll take over as Shido.
I have quite the observant eye.
I won't goof around like I did before.
Even if you're gone,
no one will suspect a thing.
Natsumi, you're...
Oof! You go look somewhere else!
I'll be the one to find Shido!
That's my line!
I can't leave him up to you.
Huh?
There's two Shidos?
What's this?
Tohka, Origami! Listen!
--This guy--
--This guy is an imposter!
He's the fake who's been
harassing everybody!
Don't be fooled! I'm the real one!
You're full of it! I'm the real one!
In other words, we have
to pick out the imposter?
A baffling situation...
But, if I had to say...
You're the imposter!
What are you talking about, you two?!
I'm the real--
You are not Shido!
Sure, you look like Shido,
but he has a different smell!
If you were all alone,
I may have been deceived.
But, standing next to the
real Shido, it's a different story.
"Shido A"
"Shido B"
Compared to the real Shido,
you blink 50 milliseconds faster.
And your center of gravity
is angled 0.2 degrees left.
There's no mistaking it!
What's wrong with these girls?
They're messed up!
Well, I can't deny it...
Unbelievable!
Unbelievable! Unbelievable!
You're...!
Unforgivable!
Not only was my secret seen...
My flawless disguise was
seen right through!
Never! I'll never acknowledge it!
You're not off the hook just yet!
H-Hey!
Shido...
Who in the world was that?
What's your relationship with her?
No, that's... Um...
It's been five days...
No movement from Natsumi either.
What's she planning to do?
Oh? That wasn't the sofa. It's Shido.
Kotori, seriously?
Aren't you a bit too relaxed?
Whatever the reason,
Natsumi views you as her enemy.
You'll never be able to seal her power
unless you raise her happiness.
I-I know that already.
There's no knowing when
she'll next appear, but...
"Shido Itsuka"
Look. This showed up in the post.
"Natsumi"
That's...?
"Shido Itsuka"
I never opened it, but I
checked it was safe at least.
"Natsumi"
So it shouldn't go "boom"
or anything like that.
This is...
A photo of me?
Twelve of them...
Also...
"Among them, I'm there.
Can you guess who I am?
Before everyone is gone.
--Natsumi."
What's it mean?
If we take the message at face value...
Among these 12 people here,
Natsumi is already using her
powers to impersonate someone.
Someone?
Which means...
It's also possible that it's me.
Shido. This is a challenge from Natsumi.
Unless you guess which person she is...
I imagine somebody will disappear.
Find her, Shido.
Before we're all gone.
Date.
So sweet, agonizing, and beloved...
The curtains are raised.
Now, for the third time.
"Episode Two:
'Can You Find Me?'"